const wordpressquestions = {
    time: 50, //in minutes
    questions: [
        {
            question: "1. WordPress is a ___?",
            option1: "Content Management System",
            option2: "Blogger",
            option3: "Programming language",
            option4: "All of these",
            correctresponse: "Content Management System",
            explanation: "WordPress is a content management system.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "2. CMS stands for ___?",
            option1: "Content Management System",
            option2: "Creator Management System",
            option3: "Content Manager Source",
            option4: "None of these",
            correctresponse: "Content Management System",
            explanation: "CMS stands for Content Management System.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "3. Which type of data can be stored in WordPress as media?",
            option1: "Text",
            option2: "Document",
            option3: "Music",
            option4: "All of these",
            correctresponse: "All of these",
            explanation: "WordPress can store all data such as text, photos, music, documents, etc.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "4. When was WordPress released?",
            option1: "May 2003",
            option2: "July 2003",
            option3: "May 2001",
            option4: "None of these",
            correctresponse: "May 2003",
            explanation: "WordPress was initially released on 27th May 2003 by Matt Mullenweg and Mike Little.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "5. Is WordPress free to use?",
            option1: "Yes",
            option2: "No",
            option3: "it is very costly only elon musk can efford it",
            option4: "Nothing is free",
            correctresponse: "Yes",
            explanation: "WordPress is an open-source platform and is free to use.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "6. Which of these is a feature of WordPress?",
            option1: "User Management",
            option2: "Provides tools for Search Engine Optimization",
            option3: "Contains multiple themes to style our website",
            option4: "All of these",
            correctresponse: "All of these",
            explanation: "Features of WordPress include managing multiple users, managing media files, library of multiple themes to style website, library of multiple plugins that provide functionalities, and allowing translation to multiple languages.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "7. Which of these is an advantage of WordPress?",
            option1: "PHP requirement",
            option2: "SEO tools make on-site SEO easier",
            option3: "Frequent updates require multiple backup copies.",
            option4: "All of these",
            correctresponse: "SEO tools make on-site SEO easier",
            explanation: "WordPress features SEO tools that make on-site SEO easier.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "8. Which of these is a free WordPress domain name provided to WordPress.com users?",
            option1: "yoursite.WordPress.org",
            option2: "Yoursite.org",
            option3: "yousite.WordPress.com",
            option4: "None of these",
            correctresponse: "yousite.WordPress.com",
            explanation: "WordPress.com provides a free website for free users under the subdomain of WordPress.com.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "9. Can you get a custom name using WordPress.com?",
            option1: "Yes",
            option2: "No",
            option3: "i dont know",
            option4: "i will not tell you",
            correctresponse: "Yes",
            explanation: "A custom domain name for a site can be claimed in WordPress for personal, premium, business plan users.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "10. Which WordPress type can be installed on a user's computer?",
            option1: "WordPress.com",
            option2: "WordPress.org",
            option3: "Both",
            option4: "None of these",
            correctresponse: "WordPress.org",
            explanation: "The WordPress.org type of WordPress can be downloaded and installed on your physical system.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "11. Which database is required by WordPress?",
            option1: "MySQL",
            option2: "MongoDB",
            option3: "RDB",
            option4: "None of these",
            correctresponse: "MySQL",
            explanation: "WordPress requires a MySQL database for its installation.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "12. Which of these fields is not required to be filled while first installing the WordPress?",
            option1: "Site Title",
            option2: "Username",
            option3: "Post",
            option4: "All of these",
            correctresponse: "Post",
            explanation: "The post of a WordPress blog is not needed at the time of installing WordPress. It can be added later on to the website.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "13. The Quick draft section in WordPress is used for ___?",
            option1: "Creating mini-posts with titles and small details",
            option2: "Editing posts",
            option3: "Creating pages",
            option4: "All of these",
            correctresponse: "Creating mini-posts with titles and small details",
            explanation: "The quick draft section in WordPress is used to create posts with only titles and basic points.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "14. Which of these is displayed using the WordPress news widget?",
            option1: "Software version",
            option2: "Software updates",
            option3: "Alerts",
            option4: "All of these",
            correctresponse: "All of these",
            explanation: "The new widget in WordPress displays the latest news from WordPress like the latest software version, updates, alerts, news, etc.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "15. Which of these is not seen on the WordPress dashboard?",
            option1: "Site traffic",
            option2: "Menu options",
            option3: "Welcome text",
            option4: "All of these",
            correctresponse: "Site traffic",
            explanation: "In the WordPress dashboard, there is no option/tab to see the site traffic.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "16. Which of these are general settings of WordPress?",
            option1: "Site title",
            option2: "Data format",
            option3: "Time format",
            option4: "All of these",
            correctresponse: "All of these",
            explanation: "The general settings page contains options such as site title, site tagline, updating site address, timezone, data format, time format, etc.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "17. Can writing settings be changed in WordPress?",
            option1: "Yes",
            option2: "No",
            option3: "i dont know",
            option4: "mute",
            correctresponse: "Yes",
            explanation: "WordPress consists of a setting option titled Writing Setting which allows its users to update writing settings for all the posts on the WordPress site.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "18. What is the default post Category for WordPress?",
            option1: "The first category added on WordPress",
            option2: "Uncategorized",
            option3: "No category",
            option4: "None of these",
            correctresponse: "Uncategorized",
            explanation: "The default post category for WordPress posts is uncategorized.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "19. What content of post can be displayed in the feed?",
            option1: "Full post",
            option2: "Summary of post",
            option3: "Optional both A and B",
            option4: "None of these",
            correctresponse: "Optional both A and B",
            explanation: "WordPress provides users an option to choose between the content of posts that can be displayed in the feeds. They are: Full post i.e. displaying all contents of the post, Summary of post. The default is full post but you can change it in the reading section.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "20. What task does search engine visibility performs in WordPress?",
            option1: "Removes site visibility on Google",
            option2: "Discourage search engines from indexing the site",
            option3: "Both",
            option4: "None of these",
            correctresponse: "Removes site visibility on Google",
            explanation: "The search engine visibility is a check on indexing of the site and when toggles off, it discourages search engines from indexing the site.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "21. What is the current version of WordPress (Feb 2022)?",
            option1: "5.8.7",
            option2: "5.9.1",
            option3: "2",
            option4: "None of these",
            correctresponse: "5.9.1",
            explanation: "As of February 2022, the most recent update of WordPress is 5.9.1.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "22. Can user-generated comments be moderated in WordPress?",
            option1: "Yes",
            option2: "No",
            option3: "never",
            option4: "i dont know",
            correctresponse: "Yes",
            explanation: "Comment moderation can be done in WordPress in the comments section to avoid spam comments on the blog.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "23. What are avatars in WordPress?",
            option1: "A small image that is displayed beside the name of the user",
            option2: "Name of creator",
            option3: "A 3D graphic of a user in WordPress",
            option4: "None of these",
            correctresponse: "A small image that is displayed beside the name of the user",
            explanation: "An avatar in WordPress is a small image that displays at the top-right-hand corner of the dashboard beside the name of the user.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "24. Where can you find permalink settings in WordPress?",
            option1: "Setting -> Permalinks",
            option2: "About -> Permalinks",
            option3: "Tools -> Links -> Permalinks",
            option4: "None of these",
            correctresponse: "Setting -> Permalinks",
            explanation: "Permalink settings can be changed by clicking settings and then clicking on permalinks.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "25. Which of these is an option to set permalink in WordPress?",
            option1: "Updating using day and name",
            option2: "Updating using month and name",
            option3: "Updating using number",
            option4: "All of these",
            correctresponse: "All of these",
            explanation: "WordPress provides the following options to update permalinks: Default, Day and name, Month and name, Post name, Number, Custom number.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "26. Can plugin files be edited in WordPress?",
            option1: "Yes",
            option2: "No",
            option3: "very good",
            option4: "i am leaving",
            correctresponse: "Yes",
            explanation: "Plugin files can be edited in WordPress.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "27. plugins in WordPress are used to ___?",
            option1: "Easily modify, customize or enhance WordPress sites",
            option2: "Change UI of the dashboard",
            option3: "Add a new address to the website",
            option4: "All of these",
            correctresponse: "Easily modify, customize or enhance WordPress sites",
            explanation: "WordPress plugins are used to easily modify, customize or enhance WordPress sites.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "28. All plugins installed on WordPress can be viewed at?",
            option1: "plugins -> add plugin",
            option2: "settings -> plugin",
            option3: "plugins -> installed plugin",
            option4: "None of these",
            correctresponse: "plugins -> installed plugin",
            explanation: "All the installed plugins on WordPress can be viewed at: plugins -> installed plugin.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "29. Is it required to activate the plugin after installing it?",
            option1: "Yes",
            option2: "No",
            option3: "yes and no",
            option4: "where am i",
            correctresponse: "Yes",
            explanation: "For working, the plugin is required to be activated after installation.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "30. Plugin update is used to ___?",
            option1: "Update some parts of plugins code based on the requirement.",
            option2: "Install an updated version",
            option3: "Add a new file to the plugin",
            option4: "All of these",
            correctresponse: "Install an updated version",
            explanation: "Updating plugin is installing a new version of the plugin in WordPress.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "31. Which of these plugins are used to check traffic on the WordPress website?",
            option1: "All in One SEO",
            option2: "Yoast",
            option3: "Jet Pack",
            option4: "All of these",
            correctresponse: "All of these",
            explanation: "All of the above plugins, Yoast, All in one SEO, Jet Pack can be used to check traffic on websites.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "32. Which of these is an anti-spam plugin in WordPress?",
            option1: "Akismet",
            option2: "BuddyPress",
            option3: "WP Forms",
            option4: "None of these",
            correctresponse: "Akismet",
            explanation: "Akismet anti-spam protection is a WordPress plugin that is used for anti-spam.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "33. Is there any plugin that allows drag and drops for creating websites in WordPress?",
            option1: "Yes",
            option2: "No",
            option3: "yes and No",
            option4: "No and yes",
            correctresponse: "Yes",
            explanation: "There are plugins and themes in WordPress that allow drag and drop creation.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "34. Which of these is not a WordPress plugin for social media?",
            option1: "WP Forms",
            option2: "Revive social",
            option3: "Smash Ballon",
            option4: "All of these",
            correctresponse: "WP Forms",
            explanation: "Revive social and smash ballon are both social media plugins in WordPress.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "35. MailPoet plugin in WordPress used to?",
            option1: "Read mails on WordPress",
            option2: "Send all info via mail in WordPress",
            option3: "Create and send the newsletter, welcome emails, etc from WordPress",
            option4: "None of these",
            correctresponse: "Create and send the newsletter, welcome emails, etc from WordPress",
            explanation: "MailPoet plugin in WordPress is used to create and send newsletters, post notifications, and welcome emails from the WordPress site.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "36. Can the size of images be reduced in WordPress?",
            option1: "Yes",
            option2: "No",
            option3: "does not support",
            option4: "i dont know",
            correctresponse: "Yes",
            explanation: "There are plugins in WordPress that can be used to compress the size of images in WordPress.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "37. Classic editor in WordPress is used to ___?",
            option1: "Change editor UI to the old style",
            option2: "Add editor to WordPress site",
            option3: "Create a new editing site",
            option4: "None of these",
            correctresponse: "Change editor UI to the old style",
            explanation: "Classic editor changes the UI for WordPress editor to an old-style one.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "38. Jetpack plugin in WordPress is used to ___?",
            option1: "Improve WordPress security",
            option2: "Increase website speed",
            option3: "Provide analytics of traffic on the site",
            option4: "All of these",
            correctresponse: "All of these",
            explanation: "The Jetpack plugin is an all-in-one plugin that can perform tasks like improving WordPress security, increasing website speed, and providing analytics of traffic on site.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "39. Can you install plugins other than the ones present in the WordPress store?",
            option1: "Yes",
            option2: "No",
            option3: "let me google it",
            option4: "No and yes",
            correctresponse: "Yes",
            explanation: "WordPress is an open platform that allows users to install plugins even if they are not present in the store. There is an 'upload plugin' option that performs the task for you.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "40. How to delete a WordPress plugin from WordPress?",
            option1: "plugin -> installed plugin -> uninstall",
            option2: "plugin -> installed plugin -> deactivate -> uninstall",
            option3: "plugin -> plugin editor -> remove",
            option4: "None of these",
            correctresponse: "plugin -> installed plugin -> deactivate -> uninstall",
            explanation: "The correct method to uninstall a WordPress plugin is: plugin -> installed plugin -> deactivate -> uninstall",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "41. Which file of WordPress themes can be skipped?",
            option1: "index.php",
            option2: "function.php",
            option3: "comments.php",
            option4: "style.css",
            correctresponse: "comments.php",
            explanation: "The comments.php file in the WordPress theme can be deleted which will hamper the view of the comment option of the theme but the theme will work.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "42. What are the different ways to change the customer's PHP version?",
            option1: "Run phphandler in EIG Shell",
            option2: "Login to Bluerock > Advanced > MultiPHP manager",
            option3: "Login to Bluerock > Advanced > MultiINI manager",
            option4: "Both A & B",
            correctresponse: "Both A & B",
            explanation: "Both of the ways mentioned in the options A and B can be used to change the customer's PHP version.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "43. Which of these plugins comes preinstalled on the WordPress site?",
            option1: "Twenty Twenty-One",
            option2: "Magazine",
            option3: "Basic theme",
            option4: "All of these",
            correctresponse: "Twenty Twenty-One",
            explanation: "For every year, the pre-installed themes are named the current year, and two previous years respectively. As of 2022, pre-installed WordPress themes are Twenty Twenty, Twenty Twenty-One, Twenty Twenty-Two.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "44. Which of these features in WordPress is not a default one?",
            option1: "Quick draft",
            option2: "View insights",
            option3: "Adding media",
            option4: "All of these",
            correctresponse: "View insights",
            explanation: "Viewing insights is an additional feature in WordPress.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "45. Can a theme other than the store be installed on WordPress sites?",
            option1: "Yes",
            option2: "No",
            option3: "let me google it",
            option4: "No and yes",
            correctresponse: "Yes",
            explanation: "There is an option to install third-party themes by uploading them.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "46. Is it possible to display a static Page as a homepage in a WordPress website?",
            option1: "Yes",
            option2: "No",
            option3: "let me google it",
            option4: "No and yes",
            correctresponse: "Yes",
            explanation: "WordPress provides an option in the reading settings to display a static Page as a homepage in a WordPress website.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "47. In WordPress themes can be edited using which of these options?",
            option1: "Using customize option",
            option2: "Editing theme code",
            option3: "Both A and B",
            option4: "None of these",
            correctresponse: "Both A and B",
            explanation: "Themes in WordPress can be edited either by clicking options present in the customize option or by editing the code of the theme.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "48. Is it possible to program your WordPress theme?",
            option1: "Yes",
            option2: "No",
            option3: "let me google it",
            option4: "No and yes",
            correctresponse: "Yes",
            explanation: "Ways are using which a WordPress theme can be created even from scratch.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "49. Which of these are built-in theme customization options in WordPress?",
            option1: "Changing site background",
            option2: "Changing site title",
            option3: "Updating copyright text in the footer",
            option4: "All of these",
            correctresponse: "All of these",
            explanation: "All of these are built-in theme customization options in WordPress.",
            time: 1
        },
        {
            question: "50. Can the theme's source code be edited in WordPress?",
            option1: "Yes",
            option2: "No",
            option3: "let me google it",
            option4: "No and yes",
            correctresponse: "Yes",
            explanation: "Theme source code can be edited in WordPress using the edit code option.",
            time: 1
        }
    ]
};


export default wordpressquestions